{
    "id": "ba1d728c76e341099ab11e88ef116f1d",
    "title": "The present perfect and present perfect continuous tense exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "590e166bbb464b70b474c1747e6e4372",
            "title": "Present Perfect And Present Perfect Continuous Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "It ……………………… continuously since morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has been raining",
                        "is raining",
                        "was raining"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We …………………… them twice, but they ………………… us yet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "visited, did not visit",
                        "have been visiting, have not visited",
                        "have visited, have not visited"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… him in a long time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was not meeting",
                        "have not met",
                        "have not been meeting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The children are hungry. They ………………….. in the garden for hours.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are playing",
                        "have been playing",
                        "were playing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ………………… each other since our school days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "know",
                        "knew",
                        "have known"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………….. you ……………….. the job?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Did, complete",
                        "Had, completed",
                        "Have, completed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her health ……………………… considerably.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "had improved",
                        "have improved",
                        "has improved"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………….. a permit.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was obtaining",
                        "have obtained",
                        "has obtained"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Those who ………………….. their work can go home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are finishing",
                        "have finished",
                        "has finished"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the fifth time you …………………. that question.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are asking",
                        "have asked",
                        "have been asking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}